TYLER ADLER

Renton, WA

(206) 718-5006

tyler.adler@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

A self-driven individual with five years of experience working in public school settings and a passion for technology. Skills include computer networking, analytical thinking, and creative problem-solving. Professional and positive demeanor, and able to apply customer service concepts to situations to improve the user experience for clients, employees, and administration.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Issaquah School District, Issaquah, WA

Custodian, April 2021 - Present

- Complete routine custodial cleaning in accordance with the Issaquah School District
- Perform required emergency cleaning services and perform minor repair work.
- Possess knowledge of and adhere to Governing Policies and District Regulations and Procedures.
- Perform other related tasks as assigned by the custodial supervisor or building administrator.

Issaguah School District Before and After School Care, Issaguah, WA

Assistant Site Coordinator, Sep 2016 - April 2021

- Supports staff to help develop them in areas in need of growth.
- Provides ideas and support to other team members to build meaningful and exciting programs.
- Communicates effectively and efficiently with parents, building staff, and program staff.
- Builds, implements, and manages activities for children ages 11-13.

Eastside Autobody LLC, Kirkland, WA

IT Consultant, Jun 2015 - Aug 2018

- Developed a website for clients and bids.
- Kept email and social accounts up to date.
- Made sure all the computers were up to date and imaged with all the bidding software and QuickBooks.
- Manage IOS and Android tablets for bidding offsite
- Tier 2 support for computer-related issues.

Issaquah School District, Issaquah, WA

Educational Assistant, Oct 2015 – Sep 2016

- Leading large groups of children on-site and on field trips.
- Adapted quickly to new surroundings and organized children to allow for a safe and fun environment.
- Assisted in any medical needs of children as well as staff.
- · Provides positive discipline and redirection when dealing with student behavior problems

EDUCATION

Bellevue College, Bellevue, WA

AAS-T Information Systems (Anticipated 2023)

Classwork: IT, Linux Support, and .NET programming

INTRESTS

 3D printing, PC Building, Classic Car Restoration, PC Gaming, Camping, and Hiking

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Windows Server Management
- Debian based server management
- Ability to Work Under Pressure
- Self-motivated
- Windows Office proficiency